Hello friends, ICICI LBAD LED has
announced its March ending quarterly numbers.
So let's see how this quarter has been
for the company.  The company has announced dividend of ₹7
per equity share.
This is for the
financial year ending 31 March 2026.
Let us now see
how the quarterly performance of the company has been.
Here are the audited
financial results of the company for the quarter ended
March 31, 2026, given here
and the figures are given in lakhs.
Before starting the video, if you have come to the channel for the
first time or you have not yet subscribed to the channel, then
please
subscribe so that you keep
getting updates of our other videos also.  So
let us first see what is the total income
of the company.  This is
for the March quarter and is worth ₹6618 crore.   In the
December quarter,
it was worth ₹6610 crore and in the
March quarter of last year, it was worth ₹5851
crore.  The company's revenue is increasing year on year.
You will see here that an
increase of 13% is visible in it.
If we talk about revenue quarter on quarter, then
you can see the revenue almost flat.  It has
increased from Rs 6610 crore to Rs 6618
crore.  A marginal increase is what
you can call it here.  Let us now see what are the
expenses after income.  There
are total expenses.
For the March quarter, it is ₹672 crore.  In the
December quarter, it was worth ₹639
crore and in the March quarter of last year, it was worth
₹5435 crore.  So
expenses are increasing year on year.  At the
same time, a marginal increase is being seen in quarter on quarter beans.
Let us now see what the profit for the
period is.
Here you will see that the profit after tax of the
company for the March quarter of the
current financial year is Rs 546 crore 56
lakh.  In the December quarter, the
profit was ₹658 crore 76 lakh and in the
March quarter of last year,
it was ₹99 crore 59 lakh.  So the
company's profit is declining quarter on
quarter.  Quarter on
quarter profit is declining by 17%.
If we talk about year on year,
then year on year increase of 7% is being seen in profit.
Profit has increased from ₹99 crore to ₹546 crore.
Let us now see what the earnings per share has been.
This is earnings per share
basic.  March is for the quarters.
Shares at ₹10.97.  In the December quarter, the
share was at ₹13.25 and in the
March quarter of last year, the
share was at ₹10.29.  So friends, this was the information about the
March ending quarterly numbers of ICICI LBD General Insurance Company.  That's all for now
in the video.
I hope
you liked the video.  If you liked the video, please
like, share and subscribe to the channel.  Thank
you.